jaldicash.com 2018-06-14

# Weizmann Impex Service Enterprise Ltd

                                                                                      Privacy Policy
                 Weizmann Impex Service Enterprise Ltd
                                          PRIVACY POLICY
The following are terms of a legal agreement (“Privacy Agreement”) concerning your privacy on
this web site l(www.jaldicash.com) between you and Weizmann Impex Service Enterprise Ltd
(WISE) , its successors , assigns, affiliates including group companies of Weizmann which
includes entities such as Weizmann Forex Limited, a RBI Registered Authorized Dealer Category-
II and one of the Principal Agents of Western Union Financial Services USA in respect of
international Inbound Money Transfer, Vedang Forex Solutions Limited a RBI Registered Full
Fledged Money Changer. By accessing, browsing and using this site you acknowledges that you
have read, understood and agree to be bound by this Privacy Agreement and to comply with all
applicable laws and regulations. We have designed this Privacy Policy to explain how we handle
personally identifiable information collected from users who register for services and submit
information to (www.jaldicash.com) through the Internet. If you do not agree to these terms,
do not use this site. Read this Privacy Agreement carefully and be aware that Weizmann Impex
Service Enterprise Ltd WISE may amend this Privacy Agreement at any time without notice and
by posting the amended terms on this site. If you have questions about www.jaldicash.com
privacy practices, please contact us at jaldicash@weizmannimpex.com.
Weizmann Impex Service Enterprise Privacy Principles:
Our core businesses include technology enabled services i.e. “Jaldi Cash” a unique payment
instrument available for Indian consumer, which is safe and convenient to transact. It is a smart
option for all, and the safest online and on–mobile transaction instrument. Jaldi Cash may be
used for transferring funds to Banks accounts, other Jaldi Cash Card (instrument holders),
making payment of utility bills & essential services. Jaldi Cash is a full usage product which
empowers you to do online transactions at any time and from anywhere or through any of our
authorized Franchisee / Retail Outlets. Through our portfolio of varied online services, spanning
from Travel booking to Insurance, from Utility Bill Payments to Mobile Top-ups, we plan to add
new dimensions to the business of retailing. These are confidential matters and Jaldi Cash and
its affiliates recognize your expectations regarding privacy policy of WISE. WISE is committed to
keep your information confidential and secure and that is why we have designed procedures to
ensure your privacy in all facets of our relationship. No matter if you are our Merchant,
business partner, franchisee / retailer, backend user, a consumer, and a customer you are
protected, not only by the applicable privacy laws, but, more importantly, commitment of WISE
to safeguard your privacy and your right to decide how your personal information will be used.
Scope of Privacy Policy:
This Privacy Policy covers treatment of personally identifiable information collected by WISE
from our merchants, franchisees and registered users who use the Jaldi Cash Services, it
payment gateway services, as well as Merchants’ information that we have tie-up and acquire
                                                                                                   1

                                                                                       Privacy Policy
in the course of our business. This Policy also covers the treatment of personally identifiable
information that our back end technology service providers / partners may share with us.
This Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that WISE does not own or control or
to people that WISE does not employ or manage. This Policy is specific to WISE and does not
apply to other Web sites, links or Internet services that are part of or to be part of the Network
of WISE.
What Personally Identifiable Information is collected by Jaldi Cash?
Jaldi Cash collects and stores information collected from our customers, franchises and end
users who use the Jaldi Cash Services, its payment gateway services, as well as Merchants,
business partners, that we have tied-up and acquired in the course of our business and some
visitor information regarding usage of this website, such as date and time of day you access our
website, browser type, browser language, the Internet Protocol (IP) address of the computer
you are using, number of hits, the pages visited, previous/subsequent sites visited and length of
user session. WISE does not collect any unique information about you (such as your name, e-
mail address, etc.) except when you specifically and know WISE only provide such information.
Objective:
1. Provide consumers notice of our information practices.
2. Offer consumers choices as to how their information is used beyond the purpose for which
     the information was provided.
3. Offer consumers reasonable access to their information and an opportunity to correct
     inaccuracies.
4. Take reasonable steps to protect the security and integrity of personal information.
WISE respects your privacy and wants to promote trust and confidence on the internet. As
such, WISE feels it is necessary to disclose to you what information this site collects and tracks
and what we do with the information that we collect.
Information security is critical to our business. We work to protect the security of your
information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts
information you input. We store information gathered on secure computers. It is important for
you to protect against unauthorized access to your Login ID/password and to your computer.
Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer and otherwise protect the password
used to access the services of WISE.
Currently, WISE collects information of our customers, franchises and end users who use the
Jaldi Cash payment gateway services, as well as Merchants, business partners that we have
tied-up and acquired in the course of our business. WISE asks merchants and customers to
supply various personal data when placing an order, such as name and address, telephone
number, and E-mail address. WISE uses this data only for the purpose of filling an order, or
                                                                                                    2

                                                                                     Privacy Policy
communicating with the customer or Merchants about the status of an order. The data so
collected is used in the aggregate to give us demographic information about the entire services
of WISE in order to improve the said service to you, to perform statistical analysis of the
collective characteristics and behavior of our Merchants, customers/users and visitors, to
measure overall patron demographics and interests regarding specific areas of the
jaldicash.com domain and to analyze how and where to use our resources. We use cookies to
help us determine which sites users’ link to, and which services merchants and visitors use.
We also track information like the domain name from which you contact us, the pages you
request, the products you buy, the referring site, and the time that you spend on the site. For
everyone who visits our website, Sub-Merchant purchase page, we log IP addresses, the type of
operating system that your computer uses, and the type of browser software used by you.
From the IP address, we can determine the Internet Service Provider and the geographic
location of your point of connectivity.
If you are our Merchant or franchisee then the personal information you provide – name,
address, etc.-allows us to inform you about updates, or changes to the service and to notify you
of products and services of WISE, its backend service providers and affiliates that we believe
may be of interest to you.
How WISE uses and share Personally-Identifiable Information:
At our website, we will use your personal details and information we obtain from other sources
to provide you with our goods and services, for administration and customer services, to
analyze your preferences and to ensure that the content, services and advertising we offer are
tailored to your needs and interests. Personally identifiable consumer information is also
shared with third parties (such as our Merchants, Banks and credit card/prepaid card
processors, franchises, business partners, and channel network) service providers, agents to the
extent necessary for WISE to deliver payment settlement/processing services. WISE may also
link to a wide variety of other sites/links. We are not responsible for their privacy policies or
how they treat information about their users. We may disclose personal data in order to
comply with a legal or regulatory obligation.
If you (i.e. our Merchant, business partner, franchises, aggregators) would like to view the
information we have collected from you and your customers or you want to correct your
information or the billing/shipping details of your customers or their IP addresses, Please go to
Login page and log into your account to view the above details and to review your personal
information. If you have questions or suggestions, we can be reached by email
at jaldicash@weizmannimpex.com.
Cookies:
The information mentioned above is gathered by using cookie. A cookie is a small line of text
that is stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. Our cookies do not contain any
personally identifiable information.
                                                                                                  3

                                                                                       Privacy Policy
We use cookies to collect information about how this site is used. We use this information to
improve how our website caters for your needs and to identify any technical problems.
Cookies are small bits of data that are stored by your browser. You can accept or decline
cookies by modifying the settings of your web browser.
When you visit our website, we may also log your IP address, a unique identifier for your
computer or other access device.
The internet is worldwide and if you are visiting this site from outside India, your visit will
necessarily result in the transfer of information across international borders. By visiting this site
and communicating electronically with us you are consenting to these transfers.
If you provide us with information about another person, you confirm that they have appointed
you to act for them, to consent to the processing of their personal data including sensitive
personal data and that you have informed them of our identity and the purposes (as set out
above) for which their personal data will be processed.
We link to a wide variety of other sites and we display advertisements from third parties on our
site. We are not responsible for the content or privacy policies of these sites and third party
advertisers, or for the way in which information about their users is treated. In particular,
unless expressly stated, we are not agents for these sites or advertisers nor are we authorized
to make representations on their behalf.
Notice:
When you complete an application form or register on our website, be aware that you are
giving WISE your personal information and you will not be informed separately. If you decide
not to complete the application form or to leave the site altogether, we will not keep any data
you have provided.
Access:
We respect your privacy rights, particularly your right to access your information. If you ask us,
and to the extent provided by local law, we will share with you the personal information we
collect and retain about you through our web-sites. We strive to keep your data accurate.
Please provide us with any changes or corrections in your information.
Data Security:
WISE strive to keep the level of security state-of-the-art at all times and takes steps to protect
your personally identifiable information and has adopted generally accepted standards of
technology in order to protect your personally identifiable information. We work to protect the
security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software,
which encrypts information you input. We store information gathered on secure computers.
We use advanced security technology to prevent our computers from being accessed by
unauthorized persons.
                                                                                                    4

                                                                                       Privacy Policy
We respond to subpoenas, warrants, or other court orders regarding information that is
contained within our access logs concerning any Merchant, business partner, agent, franchise,
end users, customer or visitor. We reserve the right to release that information concerning any
Merchant, business partner, agent, franchises; user who we believe is in violation of our
content guidelines, even without a subpoena, warrant, or other court order. We cooperate with
law enforcement agencies in identifying those who use our servers and services for illegal
activities.
We also reserve the right to report any illegal activity by our Merchants, agents, franchises or
their customers to law enforcement for prosecution.
Please be aware that WISE does not control the acts of its Merchants, agents, franchises,
customers, users or visitors. All Merchants, franchisees, customers and visitors should be aware
that, when they disclose personal information such as their actual name, store’s name, e-mail
address, etc. to third parties, the information may be collected and used by others to send that
person unsolicited e-mail from other parties, outside of WISE. In the event that you encounter
any Merchant, agent, franchises, customer of WISE or user who is improperly collecting or using
information about users, please contact us by emailing at jaldicash@weizmannimpex.com .
This website takes measures to protect its data that contains information related to you.
However, as a consideration for viewing this site or interacting with this site in any manner, you
waive all claims of any nature against this site concerning the loss, alteration, or misuse of
information. You must assume that it is possible for your personal data to be obtained by
others, such as “hackers,” and used in an inappropriate manner that may cause harm to you
and that you agree that WISE is not responsible to provide any damages to you.
ENFORCEMENT: The laws of the India provide for measures to enforce your privacy rights. In
addition, if you feel that Jaldi Cash has violated this Statement on Privacy in any way, please
contact us at jaldicash@weizmannimpex.com.
Transfer of Information Abroad:
This site may be viewed anywhere in the world. Personally identifiable information collected by
WISE through this site may be transferred to offices of WISE located all over India and the site
viewed by any person outside India. Some destination countries may not have laws that
regulate the use and transfer of such information. By using this website and posting
information on this site, you voluntarily consent to such transfer of information.
DISCLAIMER:
WISE cannot ensure that all of your personally identifiable information will never be disclosed
in ways not described in this Privacy Policy. For example, we may be required to disclose
personally identifiable information to the government or by court order under certain
circumstances, or other situations may arise requiring such disclosure. In addition, you
authorize us to disclose any information about you to law enforcement or other government
officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate.
                                                                                                    5

                                                                                    Privacy Policy
In some cases, we may share your data with third parties and affiliates in order to offer you
other services.
This site contains links to other websites. `WISE is not responsible for the privacy practices or
the content of such Websites.
YOUR USE OF OUR WEBSITE MEANS THAT YOU ARE ACCEPT THE PRACTICES SET FORTH IN THIS
POLICY. WE RESERVE THE RIGHT TO MAKE CHANGES TO THE POLICY BY POSTING THE NEW
VERSION WITH A NEW EFFECTIVE DATE AND YOUR CONTINUED USE INDICATES YOUR
AGREEMENT TO THE CHANGES.
Latest Update
This Privacy Policy was last updated on: [SEPTEMBER 2015]
                                                                                                 6
